<resources>
    <string name="app_name">homework</string>
    <string name="dennis_ritchies_biography"><![CDATA[Dennis MacAlistair Ritchie (September 9, 1941 – c. October 12, 2011) was an American computer scientist. He created the C programming language and, with long-time colleague Ken Thompson, the Unix operating system. Ritchie and Thompson were awarded the Turing Award from the ACM in 1983, the Hamming Medal from the IEEE in 1990 and the National Medal of Technology from President Bill Clinton in 1999. Ritchie was the head of Lucent Technologies System Software Research Department when he retired in 2007. He was the R in K&R C, and commonly known by his username dmr.]]></string>
    <string name="tim_berners_lees_biography">Berners-Lee was born in London, England, United Kingdom, one of four children born to Mary Lee Woods and Conway Berners-Lee. His parents worked on the first commercially built computer, the Ferranti Mark 1. He attended Sheen Mount Primary School, and then went on to attend south west London\'s Emanuel School from 1969 to 1973, at the time a direct grant grammar school, which became an independent school in 1975. A keen trainspotter as a child, he learnt about electronics from tinkering with a model railway. He studied at The Queen\'s College, Oxford, from 1973 to 1976, where he received a first-class bachelor of arts degree in physics.</string>
    <string name="edsger_dijkstra_biography">Edsger W. Dijkstra was born in Rotterdam. His father was a chemist who was president of the Dutch Chemical Society; he taught chemistry at a secondary school and was later its superintendent. His mother was a mathematician, but never had a formal job. Dijkstra had considered a career in law and had hoped to represent the Netherlands in the United Nations. However, after graduating from school in 1948, at his parents\' suggestion he studied mathematics and physics and then theoretical physics at the University of Leiden. In the early 1950s, electronic computers were a novelty. Dijkstra stumbled on his career quite by accident, and through his supervisor, Professor A. Haantjes, he met Adriaan van Wijngaarden, the director of the Computation Department at the Mathematical Center in Amsterdam, who offered Dijkstra a job. He officially became the Netherlands\' first PROGRAMER in March 1952.</string>
    <string name="dennis_ritchies_brainy_Quote">UNIX is basically a simple operating system, but you have to be a genius to understand the simplicity.</string>
    <string name="tim_berners_brainy_quote">We cant blame the technology when we make mistakes.</string>
    <string name="edsger_dijkstra_brainy_quote">Computer science is no more about computers than astronomy is about telescopes.</string>
</resources>
